[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
        "options": ["Humanity", "Health", "Honour", "Household"],
        "answer": "Health"
    },

    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
        "options": ["Pocahontas", "Sleeping Beauty", "Cinderella", "Elsa"],
        "answer": "Cinderella"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim?",
        "options": ["Hangar", "Terminal", "Concourse", "Carousel"],
        "answer": "Carousel"
    },

    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?",
        "options": ["Phillips", "Flymo", "Chubb", "Ronseal"],
        "answer": "Chubb"
    },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
        "options": ["Republicanism", "Communism", "Conservatism", "Liberalism"],
        "answer": "Communism"
    },

    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which toys have been marketed with the phrase “robots in disguise”?",
        "options": ["Bratz Dolls", "Sylvanian Families", "Hatchimals", "Transformers"],
        "answer": "Transformers"
    },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What does the word loquacious mean?",
        "options": ["Angry", "Chatty", "Beautiful", "Shy"],
        "answer": "Chatty"
    },

    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?",
        "options": ["Childbirth", "Broken bones", "Heart conditions", "Old age"],
        "answer": "Childbirth"
    },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "In Doctor Who, what was the signature look of the fourth Doctor, as portrayed by Tom Baker?",
        "options": ["Bow-tie, braces and tweed jacket", "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf", "Pinstripe suit and trainers", "Cape, velvet jacket and frilly shirt"],
        "answer": "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf"
    },

    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?",
        "options": ["Ramadan", "Diwali", "Lent", "Hanukkah"],
        "answer": "Diwali"
    },

    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
        "options": ["Bahamas", "US Virgin Islands", "Turks and Caicos Islands", "Bermuda"],
        "answer": "Bahamas"
    },

    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Construction of which of these famous landmarks was completed first?",
        "options": ["Empire State Building", "Royal Albert Hall", "Eiffel Tower", "Big Ben Clock Tower"],
        "answer": "Big Ben Clock Tower"
    }
]